<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Live. Think. Code.]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Live. Think. Code.]]></description>
        <link>http://sethryandesantis.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 08:46:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://sethryandesantis.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 08:46:10 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Map-Wall Live January 14th, 2017 at the California Science Center in Los Angeles! ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/43ab6030-e7cb-41e7-bd83-853cc9c796a6.jpg">,<h1>Map-Wall Live January 14th, 2017 at the California Science Center in Los Angeles! </h1>,<p>We went live January 14th, 2017!  Check out the exhibit I did all the coding for at the California Science Center in Los Angeles. Map-Wall is simple to use and requires users to point the spotlight at one of the several points of interest on the map and press the trigger, which causes information on the monitor to be displayed about the selected point.<br>This projects backend was written in all C++ that leveraged ultraDMX Micro for interfacing with DMX512, SEI Absoluter Encoder Comm Protocol for reading (X,Y) coordinates, and U-HID for the LED Push Buttons on the spotlight device. <br>The frontend parses JSON generated by an Excel file filled out by the exhibit currator which the code supports English and Spanish which users can change with a button press on the base of the device. The frontend is generated on the fly using basic HTML,CSS, and Javascript leveraging the dojo toolkit. All points are pre-calibrated for each station with extra space for more in the future. <br>This has been one of my favorite projects I have done thus far. It is is awesome to see people of all ages interacting with and enjoying the exhibit! </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://sethryandesantis.com/map-wall-in-production/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9bf36781-71b9-4428-9bc7-f053abe898ab</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 21:27:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>